http://www.bridgewatersavings.com/privacy/

Bluestone BankSkip to Main ContentEmploymentLocationsResourcesAbout UsPersonal BankingPersonal BankingBusiness BankingCash ManagementCredit Card AccessPersonal Online Banking User IDLoginCash Management Company IDCash Management User IDLoginEnrollNeed Help?ico-mobile-menu
MenuSearch for Products and ServicesSearchico-homeHomeico-locationLocationsico-mobile-searchSearchico-mobile-close
Close
Mobile NavigationContact UsProducts & ServicesProducts & ServicesPersonalPersonalChecking AccountsSavings & Money MarketCDs & IRAsHome EquityAdditional ServicesYour Personal BankersPersonal Online BankingBSB MobileBusinessBusinessChecking AccountsMoney Market AccountBusiness LoansCommercial Real Estate FinancingRetirement PlanningAdditional ServicesYour Business BankersBusiness Online BankingGovernmentMortgage CenterMortgage CenterMortgage OptionsHome EquityGrant ProgramMortgage RatesHome Buying ResourcesYour Loan OfficersWorkshopsOnline Mortgage AccessFinancial PlanningFinancial PlanningTrust ServicesInvestmentsInsuranceEstate PlanningYour Financial Planning TeamWorkshopsCalculatorsCurrent RatesResourcesAbout UsChoose an AccountApply for a LoanEmploymentOnline Banking LoginPersonal BankingPersonal BankingBusiness BankingCash ManagementCredit Card AccessPersonal Online Banking User IDLoginCash Management Company IDCash Management User IDLoginEnrollNeed Help? Search for Products and ServicesSearchclose searchHomePrivacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyRev 10/2020FACTSWHAT DOES BRIDGEWATER SAVINGS BANK DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?Why?Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.What?The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:Social Security number and incomeAccount balances and payment historyTransaction history and credit historyWhen you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.How?All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers’ personal information; the reasons Bluestone Bank chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.Reasons we can share your personal informationDoes Bluestone Bank share?Can you limit this sharing?For our everyday business purposes -such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureausYesNoFor our marketing purposes -to offer our products and services to youYesNoFor joint marketing with other financial companiesYesNoFor our affiliates' everyday business purposes –information about your transactions and experiencesNoWe don't shareFor our affiliates' everyday business purposes –information about your creditworthinessNoWe don't shareFor affiliates to market to youNoWe don't shareFor nonaffiliates to market to youNoWe don't shareQuestions?Call 800.356.8622Who we areWho is providing the notice?Bluestone BankWhat we doHow does Bluestone Bank protect my personal information?To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.How does Bluestone Bank collect my personal information?We collect your personal information, for example, when youOpen a deposit account, apply for a loan, pay your bills, or deposit moneyOpen a trust or investment account andShow your government-issued ID.We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates or other companies.Why can't I limit all sharing?Federal law gives you the right to limit onlysharing for affiliates for everyday business purposes - information about your creditworthinessaffiliates from using your information to market to yousharing for nonaffiliates to market to youDefinitionsAffiliatesCompanies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial or nonfinancial companies.Bluestone Bank has no affiliates.Non-affiliatesCompanies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial or nonfinancial companies.Bluestone Bank does not share with nonaffiliates so they can market to you.Joint MarketingA formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products and services to you.Our joint marketing partners include financial services companies.Current RatesSecurity CenterRouting Number: 211372828Footer NavigationHomeContact UsPatriot ActPrivacy PolicySite IndexTerms of Use Equal Housing Lender. Member FDIC. Member DIF. NMLS ID: 403265
© 2002-2020 Bluestone Bank. All rights reserved.
